<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE chapter PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.5//EN" "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.5/docbookx.dtd" [
<!ENTITY % BOOK_ENTITIES SYSTEM "manual.ent">
<!ENTITY PRODUCT "Documentation">
<!ENTITY BOOKID "manual">
<!ENTITY YEAR "2015">
<!ENTITY HOLDER "Eneo Tecnología S.L. |">
]>
<chapter>
	<title>What is redborder?</title>
	<para><emphasis role="bold">redBorder</emphasis> is a real-time network visibility and active cybersecurity platform based on Big Data and Open Source.</para>
	<para>This platform is composed of a series of Apps which collect data (through sensors placed in the network) for analysis or active security management of the network through the redborder web platform.</para>
	<para>As will be shown, depending on the applications in the platoform, the user will visualize different options in the menu bar.</para>
	<para>The Apps available in this new redborder version are the following:</para>
	<itemizedlist mark="bullet">
		<listitem>
			<para>Flow</para>
		</listitem>
		<listitem>
			<para><emphasis role="bold">IPS</emphasis></para>
		</listitem>
		<listitem>
			<para>Social</para>
		</listitem>
		<listitem>
			<para>Malware</para>
		</listitem>
	</itemizedlist>
	<section>
		<title>What is an IDS?</title>
		<para>An <emphasis role="bold">IDS</emphasis> is an Intrusion Detection System in the network(s) to protect an organization.</para> 
		<para>It tends to be a specific software that runs in the user space and that inspects the traffic reflected (Mirror/ SPAN port) in a system interface or circulates between two interfaces joined by a bridge (software switch).</para>
		<para>The said traffic is analyzed by searching for anomalies, specific signatures or suspicious behavior.</para> 
		<para>The objective of the IDS is <emphasis role="bold">to detect intrusions and issue alerts without interfering with the organization's traffic.</emphasis></para>
    </section>
    <section>
		<title>What is an IPS?</title>
		<para>An <emphasis role="bold">IPS</emphasis> is an Intrusion Prevention System in the organization's network(s).</para> 
		<para>Its operation is identical to that of the IDS (in fact it is usually the same software with an adapted behavior), except in this case it does interfere with the organization's traffic, 
		such that when a communication related to a system attack is detected, you can choose not only to <emphasis role="bold">launch alerts but also to discard the said communication's packets, creating the same effect as a firewall.</emphasis></para>
		<section>
			<title>Basic scenario for the installation of redborder</title>
			<para>A typical basic scenario proposed for the solution consists of a group of sensors arranged at different sensitive points in the organization's network 
			that will connect to a Manager or cluster of Managers to be managed and monitored.</para>
			<para>The said points consist of network links, called segments, through which the sensitive traffic will circulate and which the sensor will analyze more or less transparently, 
			according to the operating mode configured (IPS/IDS).</para>
			<para>Some fundamental aspects should be kept in mind in planning the installation of sensor equipment:</para> 
			<itemizedlist mark="circle">
				<listitem>
					<para><emphasis role="bold">The bypass segments</emphasis> (specific paired network interfaces, normally with bypass support) will be inserted in the middle of the traffic to be analyzed.</para>
				</listitem>
				<listitem>
					<para><emphasis role="bold">The management interfaces </emphasis> (bonding) for remote access both from normal machines and from the Manager.</para>
				</listitem>
				<listitem>
					<para><emphasis role="bold">IPMIs for the remote management of the hardware</emphasis> (Serial Over Lan (SOL) connection, iKVM IPMI commands such as start, restart, and turn off).</para>
				</listitem>
			</itemizedlist>
			<para>For the <emphasis role="bold">Manager,</emphasis> since specific hardware is not necessary, the only condition is <emphasis role="bold">the presence of at least two network interfaces. </emphasis></para>
			<para>This allows for, a bonding for the management and connection of sensors and another bonding (optional) for communications to other networks. Both systems support the 802.1q standard for virtual LAN (opctional when configuring).</para>
			<warning>
				<title>Warning</title>
				<para>IT IS VERY IMPORTANT that the configuration of the Manager (or cluster of Managers) be performed first before configuring and registering the sensors.</para>
				<para>The Mangaer must be operational and in a network accesible to the sensors. Some of the sensor configuration processes depend on access to the Manager. <footnote><para>The installation scenario for the redborder Manager is the same independently of the sensors being installed and registered (IPS, Flow, Malware (beta) or Vault (beta)</para></footnote>.</para>
			</warning>
			<mediaobject>
				<imageobject>
					<imagedata scalefit="1" align="center" width="350" fileref="images/ch01_img001.png"/>
				</imageobject>
				<textobject>
					<phrase>Basic scenario for the installation of the Manager</phrase>
				</textobject>
				<caption>
					<para>Basic scenario for the installation of the Manager</para>
				</caption>
			</mediaobject>		    
		</section>
    </section>
	<section>
		<title>Structure and functioning of the redborder installation wizard menus</title>
		<para><emphasis role="bold">Menú, submenú y línea de comandos</emphasis></para>
		<mediaobject>
			<imageobject>
				<imagedata scalefit="1" align="center" width="450" fileref="images/ch01_img002.png"/>
            </imageobject>
            <textobject>
				<phrase>Structure and functioning of the redborder installation wizard menus</phrase>
			</textobject>
			<caption>
				<para>Structure and functioning of the redborder installation wizard menus</para>
			</caption>
        </mediaobject>
		<para><emphasis>Menu</emphasis></para>
		<para>In the left margin of the screen you will find a list with the available options. To select any of them, you only need to enter in the <literal>Selection</literal>line the number or letter that corresponds to the option that you wish you select.</para>
		<para><emphasis>Submenu</emphasis></para>
		<para>If different actions can be performed on the option selected, a submenu will appear in the right margen of the screen.</para>
		<para><emphasis>Command lines/ option selector</emphasis></para>
		<para>In the lower margen, and separated from the menu and submenu graphically, we see the area where the selections should be indicated in the <literal>Selection</literal> lnie and enter the commands or data requested to execute the pertinent actions. In this area we can see the sytem date and time (UTC by default).</para>
		<section>
			<title>Selection of options</title>
			<para><emphasis role="bold">Predetermined options</emphasis></para>
			<para>In some cases, the system will show a series of predetermined options. If it is the answer to a question, the default option will be shown in capital letters.</para>
			<mediaobject>
				<imageobject>
					<imagedata scalefit="1" align="center" width="450" fileref="images/ch01_img003.png"/>
				</imageobject>
				<caption>
					<para>Selection of predetermined options</para>
				</caption>
			</mediaobject>
			<para><emphasis role="bold">Options available in the redborder installation wizard menu</emphasis></para>
			<itemizedlist mark="bullet">
				<listitem>
					<para>Selection of the default option: press <keycap>Enter.</keycap></para>
				</listitem>
				<listitem>
					<para>Other options: enter the appropriate letter or command.</para>
				</listitem>
				<listitem>
					<para>Exit: when you wanto to exit from a screen to return to the start menu, select the <literal>quit</literal> option, entering the letter <keycap>q.</keycap></para>
				</listitem>
				<listitem>
					<para>Apply changes: to save and apply changes made, select the <literal>apply</literal> option by entering the letter <keycap>a.</keycap></para>
				</listitem>
			</itemizedlist>
			<mediaobject>
				<imageobject>
						<imagedata scalefit="1" align="center" width="450" fileref="images/ch01_img004.png"/>
				</imageobject>
				<caption>
					<para>Options available in the redborder installation wizard menu</para>
				</caption>
			</mediaobject>
			<warning>
				<title>Warning</title>
				<para><literal>Need to "apply" to activate changes</literal></para>
				<para>If you see this message, you must select the option <keycap>a</keycap>. Otherwise, the system will not save or apply the changes made.</para>
			</warning>
			<mediaobject>
				<imageobject>
					<imagedata scalefit="1" align="center" width="450" fileref="images/ch01_img005.png"/>
				</imageobject>
				<caption>
					<para>Apply changes to save modifications</para>
				</caption>
			</mediaobject>
		</section>
	</section>
</chapter>
