<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE chapter PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.5//EN" "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.5/docbookx.dtd" [
<!ENTITY % BOOK_ENTITIES SYSTEM "manual.ent">
<!ENTITY PRODUCT "Documentation">
<!ENTITY BOOKID "manual">
<!ENTITY YEAR "2015">
<!ENTITY HOLDER "Eneo Tecnología S.L. |">
]>
<chapter>
	<title>Installation of the Enterprise Version redborder Manager</title>
	<para>Thanks to the installation wizard, the Manager can be configured and prepared quickly and easily without the need for specific Linux programming knowledge.</para> 
	<para>For the Manager installation, the user will have an <emphasis role="bold">ISO image</emphasis> obtained via download or through <emphasis role="bold">DVD</emphasis> facilitated by redborder. 
	If the image was obtained via download, you can download it to your local disk or save it to a DVD or USB to be installed on a physical machine. In any case, once the first phase of installation is done, 
	the system will restart and will boot up from the default option: <literal>Select from local disk.</literal></para>
	<para>Upon booting up, the installation wizard will have access to a menu with the following options:</para>
	<itemizedlist mark="bullet">
		<listitem>
			<para><literal>Install Manager:</literal> launches the Managr installation menu.</para>
		</listitem>
		<listitem>
			<para><literal>Install Sensor:</literal> this option allows you to install the appropriate sensor for its subsequent registration in the redborder Manager.
			 <footnote><para>Depending on the solution acquired, the menu will show the different options for the installation and registration of the sensors of the different Apps in the Manager:
			 IPS (App IPS), Instagram or Twitter (App Social), MailGateway, Endpoint or ProxyHTTP (Malware App).</para></footnote></para>
		</listitem>
		<listitem>
			<para><literal>Rescue installed system:</literal> rescue start mode for cases where your machine has problems starting (advanzed mode). 
			It also allows you to start the process of resolving the problem or changing the user password if it has been lost.</para>
		</listitem>
		<listitem>
			<para><literal>Boot from Local Drive:</literal> boot up from the local disk (by default).</para>
		</listitem>
	    <listitem>
			<para><literal>Memory Test:</literal> memory test available for the system installation. If a memory module is defective, this test will detect it and will advise the user.</para>
		</listitem>
	</itemizedlist>
	<note>
		<title>Note</title>
		<para>Cluster Creation: it is advisable to revise the machine's memory before starting the installation of the second Manager.</para>
	</note>
	<mediaobject>
		<imageobject>
			<imagedata scalefit="1" align="center" width="450" fileref="images/ch02_img001.png"/>
		</imageobject>
		<textobject>
			<phrase>Main screen of the redborder Manager installation wizard</phrase>
		</textobject>
			<caption>
				<para>Main screen of the redborder Manager installation wizard</para>
			</caption>
	</mediaobject>
    <para>The installation process of the Manager will be carried out in two steps:</para>
	<itemizedlist mark="circle">
		<listitem>
			<para>Basic settings and installation of the packets:</para>
			<para>a) Lanaguage selection</para>
			<para>b) Keyboard selection</para>
			<para>c) Enter password</para>
		</listitem>
		<listitem>
			<para>Completion of the Manager installation:</para>
			<para>a) Network configuration</para>
			<para>b) System configuration</para>
		</listitem>
	</itemizedlist>   
    <para>Select <literal>Install Manager</literal> to begin the installation process of the Manager. Below, a series of basic configurations is explained.</para>
    <section>
		<title>Manager installation process: basic settings</title>
		<para><emphasis role="bold">a) Language selection</emphasis></para>
		<para>Select the language in which you would like to operate from now on.</para> 
		<mediaobject>
			<imageobject>
				<imagedata scalefit="1" align="center" width="450" fileref="images/ch02_img002a.png"/>
			</imageobject>
			<textobject>
					<phrase>Basic settings: language selection</phrase>
				</textobject>
				<caption>
					<para>Basic settings: language selection</para>
				</caption>
		</mediaobject>
		<para><emphasis role="bold">b) Keyboard selection</emphasis></para>
		<para>Choose the type of keyboard you would like to use during the process. Due to its broad compatibility, the American [US] keyboard option is selected by default.</para>
		<mediaobject>
			<imageobject>
				<imagedata scalefit="1" align="center" width="450" fileref="images/ch02_img002b.png"/>
			</imageobject>
			<textobject>
					<phrase>Basic settings: Keyboard selection</phrase>
				</textobject>
				<caption>
					<para>Basic settings: Keyboard selection</para>
				</caption>
        </mediaobject>
        <para><emphasis role="bold">c) Enter password</emphasis></para>
        <para><emphasis>1) Choose and enter a password:</emphasis> This will be the key that you will use from now on. It can be changed at any time.</para>
        <para><emphasis>2) Confirm password:</emphasis> Enter the password again to verify that you have entered it correctly without any typographical errors. 
        If the password strength is low, the program will notify you in a pop-up window.</para>
        <para> You can choose to enter a stronger password or save the current password and change it at a later time by selecting option <keycap>3)</keycap> <literal>Password</literal>, 
        accesible from the Mangaer Configuration menu (<literal>redBorder Configuration Menu)</literal>.</para>    
        <note>
			<title>Nota</title>
			<para>Remember that the password selected in this step will be the password used to access the redborder web platform.</para>
        </note>
        <para>Once you have entered your Password selected the <literal>OK</literal> option, the system will create the 
        partitions and install the wizard packets in your hard drive.</para>
        <mediaobject>
			<imageobject>
				<imagedata scalefit="1" align="center" width="450" fileref="images/ch02_img002c.png"/>
			</imageobject>
			<textobject>
					<phrase>Basic settings: password</phrase>
			</textobject>
				<caption>
					<para>Basic settings: password</para>
				</caption>
		</mediaobject>
        <para><emphasis role= "bold">Installation of the packets and restarting the system</emphasis></para>
		<para>Once you have entered the password, the wizard will install the packets in the hard drive.</para>
		<para>Wait until the progress bar indicates that the installation has finished 100%. This process may take a few minutes.</para>
		<para>Do not press any keys or perform any actions until the process has finished completely:</para>
		<mediaobject>
			<imageobject>
				<imagedata scalefit="1" align="center" width="450" fileref="images/ch02_img002d.png"/>
			</imageobject>
			<textobject>
					<phrase>Installation of the wizard packets</phrase>
				</textobject>
				<caption>
					<para>Installation of the wizard packets</para>
				</caption>
		</mediaobject>
		<para>Once the packets are installed, the program executes the last scripts to finish the step. Then, a pop-up window will appear which requests that the system be restarted to finish the first part
		of the installation. Click on <literal>Reboot</literal>.</para>		
	</section>
    <section>
		<title>Complete the redborder Manager installation: redBorder Configuration menu</title>
		<para>After the automatic system restart, we see the next screen which we will log into using the user <literal>root</literal>:</para>	
		<mediaobject>
			<imageobject>
				<imagedata scalefit="1" align="center" width="450" fileref="images/ch02_img002e.png"/>
			</imageobject>
			<textobject>
					<phrase>Completion of the installation process: login</phrase>
				</textobject>
				<caption>
					<para>Completion of the installation process: login</para>
				</caption>
		</mediaobject>
		<para><emphasis role="bold">Login</emphasis></para>
		<note>
			<title>Note</title>
			<para>In order to install the Manager, it is necessary to log in with the user that has the most permissions: <emphasis>root.</emphasis></para>
		</note>		
		<para>For better security, we recommend that you assign three levels of users/ permissions betwen the people that will be in charge of the Manager.</para>
		<para><emphasis role="bold">Levels of users for the redborder Manager</emphasis></para>
		<orderedlist numeration="arabic">
			<listitem>
				<para><emphasis role="bold">root:</emphasis> has all permissions. It is the super-administrador of the system.</para>
			</listitem>
			<listitem>
				<para><emphasis role="bold">admin:</emphasis> user that only has access to the system configuration menu, but does not have permissions ot modify files.</para> 
			</listitem>
			<listitem>
				<para><emphasis role="bold">redborder:</emphasis> this user has a different meaning for the Manager than for the sensors.</para>
				<para>-<literal>manager</literal>: user used for the registration of sensors.</para>
				<para>-<literal>sensor</literal>: user used when the Manager wants to communicate with the sensors.</para>
			</listitem>	
		</orderedlist>    
		<para>Next the following actions will be taken:</para>
		<itemizedlist mark="bullet">
			<listitem>
				<para>Password</para>
			</listitem>
			<listitem>
				<para>rb_sysconf Command</para>
			</listitem>
		</itemizedlist>	
        <para><emphasis role="bold">Password</emphasis></para>
		<para>Enter password. This is the password that you entered in the first stage of basic settings.</para>    
	    <mediaobject>
			<imageobject>
				<imagedata scalefit="1" align="center" width="450" fileref="images/ch02_img002c.png"/>
			</imageobject>
			<textobject>
					<phrase>Complete installation process: password</phrase>
				</textobject>
				<caption>
					<para>Complete installation process: password</para>
				</caption>
		</mediaobject>	
		<para><emphasis role="bold">Enter <literal>rb_sysconf</literal></emphasis> command</para>
		<para>Execute the command <literal>rb_sysconf</literal> to launch the <literal>redBorder Configuration menu.</literal></para>
		<mediaobject>
			<imageobject>
				<imagedata scalefit="1" align="center" width="450" fileref="images/ch02_img002f.png"/>
			</imageobject>
			<textobject>
				<phrase>Completion of the installation process: enter rb_sysconf command</phrase>
			</textobject>
			<caption>
				<para>Completion of the intallation process: enter <literal>rb_sysconf</literal> command</para>
			</caption>
		</mediaobject>
		<para>These are the options that you will find on the main screen of this menu: </para>
		<orderedlist numeration="arabic">
		 	<listitem>
				<para><literal>System Configuration:</literal> configuration of the hostname, Manager IP, time and state of the Manager.</para>
			</listitem>
			<listitem>
				<para><literal>Network Configuration:</literal> creation of bondings, segments, DNS, routes and IPMI. Remember that in order put the Manager in operation, 
				at least two network connections are required.</para>
			</listitem>
			<listitem>
				<para><literal>Passwords:</literal> access this option if you want to change the passwords defined for each user role.</para>
			</listitem>
			<listitem>
				<para><literal>Backup System:</literal> allows for the creation of a recovery file, the possibility to restore the machine with a backup copy and a view of a list of the available backup copies and
				 the possibility of uploading the said files to an FTP server.	</para>
			</listitem>			
		</orderedlist>
		<para><literal>w) start simple wizard:</literal> starts a wizard that will allow you to easily and quickly install and configure the Manager.</para>
		<para><literal>q) quit:</literal> Salir. Returns us to the main system configuration screen.</para>
		<mediaobject>
			<imageobject>
				<imagedata scalefit="1" align="center" width="450" fileref="images/ch02_img003.png"/>
		    </imageobject>
		    <textobject>
					<phrase>Main screen of redborder configuration menu installtion wizard</phrase>
				</textobject>
				<caption>
					<para>Main screen of redborder configuration menu installtion wizard</para>
				</caption>
		</mediaobject>
	</section>
	<section>
		<title>Installation of the redborder Manager with Simple wizard</title>
		<para>To perform the automatic installation of the Manager, there is an option to: <keycap>w)</keycap><literal>start simple wizard</literal>.
		 This option facilitates the installation process of a Manager and the creation of a cluster for the union or two or more managers.</para>
		<important>
			<title>Important</title>
			<para>The steps that will be followed here are those corresponding to the installation of the Manager from the beginning, with additional instructions for adding another Manager to a cluster.</para>
			<para>If the Manager has already been installed, it will not be necessary to repeat the network connection. You will only have to connect the new Manager being added to the cluster. </para>
			<para>>The user will be able to manually configure the rest of the system parameters with the selection option <keycap>1)</keycap><literal>System configuration</literal> in the redBorder configuration menu.</para>
		</important>
		<para>As you will see, there are different options defined by default. To accept them, you only need to press <keycap>Enter.</keycap> 
		However, you can change them naually at any time during the installation process.</para>
		<para><emphasis role="bold">Mode, Hostname and DNS</emphasis></para>
		<mediaobject>
			<imageobject>
				<imagedata scalefit="1" align="center" width="450" fileref="images/ch02_img004.png"/>
		    </imageobject>
		    <textobject>
				<phrase>Installation with simple wizard</phrase>
			</textobject>
			<caption>
				<para>Installation with simple wizard: enter Hostname, domain, primary DNS, secondary DNS and server NTP</para>
			</caption>
		</mediaobject>
		<orderedlist numeration="arabic">
				<listitem>
					<para><literal>Selected Mode: cluster.</literal> Select the cluster mode to join more than one Manager.</para>
				</listitem>
				<listitem>
					<para><literal>Insert Hostname [rbmanager].</literal> The option defined by default is <literal>rbmanager.</literal> This is the name that clearly and simply identifies the Manager its position within the cluster.</para>
				</listitem>
				<listitem>
					<para><literal>Insert domain: [redborder.cluster].</literal> Domain defined by default.</para>
				</listitem>
				<listitem>
					<para><literal>Insert Primary DNS.</literal> Value defined by default. The user can change it to indicate the server that provides the DNS to its network and to which the Manager will be associated.</para>
				</listitem>
				<listitem>
					<para><literal>Insert Secondary DNS (optional).</literal>  Indicate secondary DNS (optional). It is recommended that an alternative DNS be entered to substitute the primary DNS in case of server error.</para>
				</listitem>
		</orderedlist>
		<note>
			<title>Note</title>
			<para>It is recommended that <emphasis role="bold">different names be used for each one of the Managers being added to the cluster.</emphasis>
			 Consecutive numbering is the most appropriate (e.g.:rbmanager01, rbmanager02), or a name which identifies the role (e.g.: rbmanagermaster, rbmanagerslave01, rbmanagerslave02).</para>
		</note>
		<para>Once these values have been entered, the system will notify that the changes have been applied successfully with the following message marked in green: <literal>DNS and domain settings applied successfully.</literal></para>
		<para><emphasis role="bold">Bonding creation</emphasis></para>
		<para> The next step to beging the bonding creation process is the indicate the NTP server: <literal> NTP server [pool.ntp.org]:</literal> 
		If there are any NTP servers in your network, this must be indicated. Otherwise, one will be assigned by default.</para>
		<para>Hereafter, the system will ask you to enter the management IP: <literal>Insert management IP address:</literal></para>
		<warning>
			<title>Warning</title>
			<para>For the creation of a cluster the user must reserve two bondings: one for the network managemet <emphasis role="bold">(Management IP address)</emphasis> 
			and another for the synchronism network <emphasis role="bold">(Sync IP address).</emphasis></para>
		</warning>
		<mediaobject>
			<imageobject>
				 <imagedata scalefit="1" align="center" width="450" fileref="images/ch02_img005.png"/>
		    </imageobject>
		    <textobject>
				<phrase>Configuring the Manager with Simple Wizard</phrase>
			</textobject>
			<caption>
				<para>Installation of the Manager with Simple Wizard: enter the management IP of the Manager</para>
			</caption>
		</mediaobject>
		<para>To create a bonding, the elements indicated hereafter must be specified. To accept the defined values, simply press the <keycap>Enter</keycap> key. Otherwise, manually enter the new values.</para>
		<itemizedlist mark="bullet">
			<listitem>
				<para><literal>Insert management Netmask</literal></para>
			</listitem>
			<listitem>
				<para><literal>Insert default gateway for this management interface (Y/n):</literal></para>
				<para>The predetermined option appears in capital letters. Remember that if you want to add this gateway just press the <keycap>Enter</keycap> key.</para>
				<para>If you want to enter a new gateway for this management interface, type <keycap>n</keycap>.</para>
			</listitem>
			<listitem>
				<para><literal>Insert default gateway</literal></para>
			</listitem>
			<listitem>
				<para><literal>Insert a route for this bonding (y/N)?:</literal></para>
				<para>Type <keycap>y</keycap> to enter a new route for the bonding.</para>
			</listitem>		
		</itemizedlist>
		<para>Once these values have been entered, the system will notify that the bonding has been created successfully with the following message marked in green: <literal>Bonding 0 created successfully.</literal></para>
		<mediaobject>
			<imageobject>
				<imagedata scalefit="1" align="center" width="450" fileref="images/ch02_img006.png"/>
		    </imageobject>
		    <textobject>
				<phrase>Bonding creation: insert the synchronism IP</phrase>
			</textobject>
			<caption>
				<para>Manager Installation with Simple Wizard: Bonding creation and insertion of synchronism IP</para>
			</caption>
		</mediaobject>
		<para><emphasis role="bold">Creating a new synchronism bonding for adding a new Manager to the cluster</emphasis></para>
		<para>To create a new bonding we must indicate the IP and the synchronism network mask as well as a route for the new bonding.</para>
		<para> Once these values have been entered, the system will notify that the bonding has been created successfully: <literal>Bonding 1 created successfully.</literal></para>
		<para>The following question will then appear: <literal>Would you like to join to another cluster (y/N)?</literal>, type <keycap>y</keycap><!--pendiente cambio en mensaje-->
		 to continue with the process of joining a new Manager to the cluster.</para>
		<warning>
			<title>Warning</title>
			<para>During the installation of the first Manager, the question <literal>Would you like to join to another cluster (Y/N)?</literal> does not apply, and so the option <keycap>N</keycap> will be defined by default.</para>
		</warning>
		<mediaobject>
			<imageobject>
				 <imagedata scalefit="1" align="center" width="450" fileref="images/ch02_img007.png"/>
		    </imageobject>
		    <textobject>
				<phrase>Creation of synchronism bonding to add a Manager to the cluster</phrase>
			</textobject>
			<caption>
				<para>Installing Manager with Simple Wizard: creating synchronism bonding to add a Manager to the cluster</para>
			</caption>
		</mediaobject>
		<para><emphasis role="bold">Synchronization with databases and storage</emphasis></para>
		<para>At this point we must tell the system how the databases and data storage will be managed in the Manager. As can be seen in the screenshot,in all cases the option <keycap>N</keycap> 
		is selected by default. It is thus recommended that the Manager perform this operation. Otherwise, select the option <keycap>y</keycap> for the following cases:</para>
		<para><literal>Would you like to use remote S3 storage? (y/N).</literal> Indicate if the Amazon Web Services (AWS) protocol is being used to transfer file.</para>
		<para><literal>Would you like to use remote memcached? (y/N).</literal> Select if you would like to perform chaching requests to databases. </para>
		<para><literal>Would you like to use remote postgresql database? (y/N).</literal> Managing with postgresql database.</para>
		<para>Once the selected option has been indicated, we must confirm that we want to apply this configuration: <literal>Are you sure you want to apply this configuration? (y/N)</literal></para>
		<para>Select the option <keycap>y</keycap>.</para>
		<mediaobject>
			<imageobject>
				<imagedata scalefit="1" align="center" width="450" fileref="images/ch02_img008.png"/>
		     </imageobject>
		     <textobject>
				<phrase>Database options</phrase>
			</textobject>
			<caption>
				<para>Installing Manager with Simple Wizard: database options</para>
			</caption>
		</mediaobject>
		<para>From now on, the installation of the selected services will be carried out. 
		This process may take a few minutes. Once the instalation has been completed, the wizard will take you back to the main screen of the redborder configuration menu.</para>
		<para>To exit the wizard, select the option <keycap>q)</keycap> <literal>quit.</literal></para>
		<para>To install a new Manager and add it to a cluster, select the option <keycap>w)</keycap> to launch the new installation wizard.</para>	
	</section>
	<section>
		<title>Installing and adding a new Manager to the cluster</title>
		<para>To install a second Manager (if it is being installed at a different time than the master Manager)
		it is necessary to launch the ISO image again to iniciate the process; the first steps are identical to those described previously fot the installation of the Manager.</para>
		<note>
			<title>Note</title>
			<para>In the main screen of the Manager installation wizard you will find the option <literal>Memory Test</literal> 
			to be advisable to review the memory status of the machine before before starting the installation of the second Manager.</para>
		</note>
		<para>Select <literal>Install Manager</literal> to initiate the installation process.</para>
		<mediaobject>
			<imageobject>
				<imagedata scalefit="1" align="center" width="450" fileref="images/ch02_img001.png"/>
			</imageobject>
			<textobject>
				<phrase>Main screen of the redborder Manager installation wizard</phrase>
			</textobject>
			<caption>
				<para>Main screen of the redborder Manager installation wizard</para>
			</caption>
		</mediaobject>
		<para>After configuring the basic settings and installing the packets, the system will restart automatically. 
		Then Log in, enter Password and enter the command in <literal>rb_sysconf</literal> 
		to access the main screen of the redborder configuration menu.</para>		
		<note>
			<title>Note</title>
			<para>The password that you select here can be different from that indicated for the first Manager. <emphasis role="bold">Using a single password is recommended to avoid confusion.</emphasis></para>
		</note>
		<mediaobject>
			<imageobject>
				<imagedata scalefit="1" align="center" width="450" fileref="images/ch02_img009.png"/>
			</imageobject>
			<textobject>
				<phrase>Installing a new Manager and adding it to the cluster</phrase>
			</textobject>
			<caption>
				<para>Installing a new Manager and adding it to the cluster</para>
			</caption>
		</mediaobject>
		<para>Select the option <keycap>w)</keycap><literal>start simple wizard</literal> to start the installation process of the second Manager. It is recommended that the default option be <literal>Selected Mode: cluster.</literal></para>
		<para>The installation process of this second Manager is identical to that employed for the installation of the master Manager. The configuration of the same elements can be observed on the following screens n the following screens:</para>
		<itemizedlist mark="circle">
			<listitem>
				<para>Hostname</para>
			</listitem>
			<listitem>
				<para>Domain</para>
			</listitem>
			<listitem>
				<para>Primary DNS (may differ from the primary Manager)</para>
			</listitem>
			<listitem>
				<para>Secondary DNS</para>
			</listitem>
			<listitem>
				<para>NTP server</para>
			</listitem>		
		</itemizedlist>
		<important>
			<title>Important</title>
			<para>It is important that <emphasis role="bold">different names for each of the Managers being added to the cluster</emphasis> be used.
			It is advisable to follow consecutive numbering (e.g.:rbmanager01, rbmanager02) or a name which identifies its role (e.g.: rbmanagermaster, rbmanagerslave01, rbmanagerslave02).</para> 
		</important>
		<para>The next step is the creation of two bondings: management (bonding 0) and sychronism (bonding 1). Indicate (or select the value given by defualt) the following values:</para>
		<itemizedlist mark="circle">
			<listitem>
				<para>(Management/sync) IP address</para>
			</listitem>
			<listitem>
				<para>(Management/sync) Netmask</para>
			</listitem>
			<listitem>
				<para>Gateway for the management interface (<literal>Default gateway for this management interface (Y/n)?:</literal>)</para>
			</listitem>
			<listitem>
				<para>Route for the bonding (<literal>Insert a route for this bonding (y/N)?:</literal>)</para>
			</listitem>
		</itemizedlist>
		<para>Once theses values have been entered, the wizard will confirm that the bondings 0 and 1 have been created successfully: <literal>Bonding created successfully.</literal></para>
		<warning>
			<title>Warning</title>
			<para>The management networks of the first and second Manager as well as the that of the synchronism must have connectivity amongst them in order to be able to function as a cluster. </para>
			<para><literal>Cluster SYNC IP Adress (bond1):</literal> Enter as synchronism IP the same IP as the Master Manager.</para>
		</warning>
		<mediaobject>
			<imageobject>
				 <imagedata scalefit="1" align="center" width="450" fileref="images/ch02_img010.png"/>
		    </imageobject>
		    <textobject>
				<phrase>Installing a new Manager and adding it to the cluster: bondings</phrase>
			</textobject>
			<caption>
				<para>Installing a new Manager and adding it to the cluster: bondings</para>
			</caption>
		</mediaobject>
		<para>In this case, when asked: <literal>Would you like to join another cluster? (y/N);</literal> select the option <keycap>y</keycap>.</para>
		<para>Next, the cluster synchronism IP must be entered: <literal>Cluster SYNC IP Adress (bond1):</literal> 
		This corresponds to the synchronism IP (or bonding 1) of the first Manager or Master. </para>
		<mediaobject>
			<imageobject>
				 <imagedata scalefit="1" align="center" width="450" fileref="images/ch02_img011.png"/>
		    </imageobject>
		    <textobject>
				<phrase>Enter the synchronism IP to add to the cluster</phrase>
			</textobject>
			<caption>
				<para>Installing a new Manager and adding it to the cluster: enter the synchronism IP to add it to the cluster</para>
			</caption>
		</mediaobject>
		<note>
			<title>Note</title>
			<para>If the machine uses DHCP, these configurations will be performed automatically.</para>
		</note>
		<para>Before applying this configuration, select the mode in which the Manager will operate. On the following screen all available options can be seen: </para>
		<mediaobject>
			<imageobject>
				 <imagedata scalefit="1" align="center" width="450" fileref="images/ch02_img012.png"/>
		    </imageobject>
		    <textobject>
				<phrase>Select services for each of the Managers</phrase>
			</textobject>
			<caption>
					<para>Installing a new Manager and adding it to the cluster: select the mode of the new Manager</para> <!--Revisar conceptos manager/esclavo-->
			</caption>
		</mediaobject>
		<note>
			<title>Note</title>
			<para>If no option has been selected, the system will attribute the option <literal>1) slave</literal> to the new Manager by default.</para>
			<para>It is recommended that slave mode be selected (<literal>1) slave</literal>) to the new Manager since, this way, both Managers share services.</para>
		</note>	
		<para>Congratulations! You have correctly installed the Enterprise Version of redborder Manager. From now on, you can configure and manage the Manager from the redborder web platform.</para>
		<para>Read Chapter 3 "Installing and registering IPS/IDS sensors" to complete the installation process of the Manager and registration of the sensors.</para>
	</section>
</chapter>
